

# **VINSENSIUS DWI CANDRA NUGRAHA**

Address: Jl. Kavling 1, Harjamukti, Cimanggis

Phone: 081293975561

Email: vinsennugraha2002@gmail.com

Website: <a href="https://vinsennugraha.github.io/Portfolio/">https://vinsennugraha.github.io/Portfolio/</a>

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a person who likes to socialize, meet and even work together with people I have just met. I am also known as a good listener so I am able to grasp the essence of the problem and provide the right solution. I am also a responsible person in carrying out my duties. Trustworthy and always interested in self-development and new experiences. I can adapt to new environments and respond quickly. I can also work together in a team and am able to communicate well.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Freelance, PT. Indoneksi Investama

Sept 2023 - Present

- Create and maintenance website-based company profile applications for training institutions
- · Create content for social media
- Sound engineer for Convention Hall and Restaurant

## Freelance, MC Klub Jakarta

Feb 2024

- · Create an online invitation in the form of a website
- · Create a festive birthday event and become a video jockey at the event

## Waiters, Semoet Coffe & Convention Hall

Jan 2020 - Jan 2021

Helping to make coffee and delivering orders

Keyboardist Jan 2020 - Present

 Accompany songs at least once a week at worship events to guide the congregation in worship

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Bachelor of Industrial Engineering**

Aug 2020 - Present

University of Gunadarma

• Major in Informatika.

## **ORGANISATIONAL EXPERIENCE**

**Head Of The Badminton Extracurricular** 

Aug 2018 - Aug 2019

SMAN 105 Jakarta Timur

Secretary Sept 2020 - Jan 2021

Natal KMK Gunadarma 2020

## **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

- Technical Skills: Computer Hardware, Networking
- Languages: English, Indonesia.
- Certifications: Fundamental Web, Fundamental Desktop, Golang For Beginner.
- Awards/Activities: Actively participated in the government program "Digital Literacy Coordination and Communication Forum".